Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project Log Contracts, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Maps Drawings, 1968 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Camp Long Improvements, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Camp Long Improvements - Project File, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Camp Long Proposed Alley Vacation, 1971 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Camp Long Handicapped Improvements, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Camp Long Handicapped Improvements, 1981 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Camp Long Handicapped Improvements Jan. - June, 1980 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Camp Long Handicapped Improvements July - Dec., 1980 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Camp Long Handicapped Improvements, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Camp Long Belay Tower, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Camp Long UPARR Funding, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Camp Long Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Outlook, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 8/27)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Outlook, 1974 (Box-folder 8/28)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Lookout, 1975 (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Lookout, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 8/30)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Lookout Project File, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 8/31)
  - Capitol Hill Viewpoint / Louisa Boren Lookout - Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 8/32)
  - Carkeek Park Contracts and Log, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion - Project Description, 1974 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Carkeek Park - Storm Drain, 1972 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion - Project File, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion Project File, 1974 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion: Project File, 1975 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion Project File, 1976 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Carkeek Park Newspaper Articles, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Carkeek Park Expansion - Financial / Funding, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Cascade Playground, 1971 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Project Description, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Central Area / Judkins Project File, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Project File Jan - April, 1974 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Project File May - Dec, 1974 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playground Jan. - June, 1975 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Judkins / Central Area Playground July - Dec., 1975 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield - Project File Jan. - April, 1976 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Project File May - December, 1976 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield: Environmental Impact Statement, 1974 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Financial, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield Contracts Project Log, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield: Contractor Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playground: Seattle Public Schools, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Central Area / Judkins Playfield: Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield: Project File, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield, 1976 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield Project File, 1977 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield - Project File Jan. - April, 1978 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield May - Dec., 1978 (Box-folder 9/31)
  - Children's Bird Bath / Heidi Peterson Memorial, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Christie Mini Park / NE 43rd St. Mini Park (includes 35mm slide of A. Fiske mural), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - City Hall Park, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 9/34)
  - Collins Recreation Center Playfield, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Colman Park Walkways, 1978 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Colman Park Walkways Jan - May, 1979 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Colman Park Walkways July - Dec., 1979 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Colman Park Walkways Jan - April, 1980 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Colman Park Walkways May - Dec, 1980 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Colman Park Walkways Jan - Dec, 1981 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Colman Park Walkways July - Dec, 1981 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Colman Park Walkways, 1982 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Colman Pool - Sanitary Sewer: Feasibility Study, 1975 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Colman Pool - Sanitary Sewer: Soil Foundation Investigation Report, 1977 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Colman Pool - Sanitary Sewer: Design Contract, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Colman Pool - Sanitary Sewer, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Colman Pool - Sanitary Sewer, 1977 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Columbia Park Improvements, 1978 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Columbia Park Improvements, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks: Proposed Park, 1949-1970 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks Jan - March, 1973 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks April - Dec, 1973 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks, 1974 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks (includes photographs), 1975 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks, 1976 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks, 1977 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks includes, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks Design Construction Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks: Environmental Impact Statements, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks Financial, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks Land Acquisition, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Commodore Park / Chittenden Locks Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1976 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Community Center Improvements: Consultant Selection, 1979 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Community Center Improvements: Design Contract - Loyal Heights Queen Anne, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Community Center Improvements: Design Contracts - Hiawatha / Arne Bystrom, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Community Center Improvements: Design Contract - Alki / Stickney Murphy, 1980 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Community Center Improvements: Ballard, Hiawatha, South Park, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Community Center Improvements: Loyal Heights, Queen Anne, Alki, 1979 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Community Center Improvements: Ballard, Hiawatha, South Park, Loyal Heights, Queen Anne, Alki, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Community Center Improvements: Queen Anne, Loyal Heights, Alki, Hiawatha April - August, 1980 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Community Center Improvements: Queen Anne, Loyal Heights, Alki, Hiawatha, 1980 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Community Center Improvements: Queen Anne, Loyal Heights, Hiawatha, Alki - Jan - March, 1981 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Community Center Improvements: Queen Anne, Loyal Heights, Hiawatha, Alki April - May, 1981 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Community Center Improvements: Budget - Analysis of Physical Condition, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Community Center Improvements: Budget, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Community Center Improvements: Alki, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Community Center Improvements: Hiawatha, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Community Center Improvements: Hiawatha, 1982 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Community Center Improvements: Hiawatha, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Community Center Improvements: Loyal Heights / Queen Anne (Includes Drawings), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Community Center Improvements: Loyal Heights, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Community Center Improvements: Queen Anne, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Community Center Improvements March - June, 1982 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Community Center Improvements: Garfield July - Dec., 1982 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Community Center Improvements: Garfield - Schematic Design Development Review, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Community Center Improvements: Garfield, 1983 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Community Center Improvements: Garfield, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Community Center Improvements: Garfield, Miller, Southwest Budget Estimate Design Development, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Community Center Improvements: Southwest, 1982 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Community Center Improvements: Southwest, 1983 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Community Center Improvements: Southwest, 1984 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Community Center Improvements: Southwest Re-roof, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Cowen Park: Project Log Design Services Contract, 1974 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Cowen Park Project File, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Cowen Park, 1975 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Dahl Playfield: Contract, 1980 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Dahl Playfield / Children's Play Area, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Dahl Playfield / Children's Play Area, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Dearborn Park / School District, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Dearborn Park - Land Acquisition, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Dearborn Park: Project Log Design Services Contract, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Dearborn Park Improvements, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Dearborn Park Improvements, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Dearborn Park Improvements (Includes Soccer Field), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Dearborn Park: Access to Private Residence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Dearborn Park: Phase II Project Logs Contracts, 1980 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Dearborn Park / Madrona Playground: Project File Phase II, 1980 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Delridge Community Center - Budget, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Delridge Community Center Design Services Contract, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Delridge Community Center: Design Development, 1978 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Delridge Community Center Project Files Jan - July, 1978 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Delridge Community Center Project File Aug. - Dec., 1978 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Delridge Community Center Project File, 1979 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Delridge Community Center Project File, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Delridge Community Center Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Delridge Playfield, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Delridge Playfield, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Denny Park Re-Roofing Contract, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Denny Park Re-Roofing Project File, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Denny Regrade - Agreement with DCD, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Denny Regrade Park - Dedication, 1979 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Denny Regrade Park - Art Work, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Denny Regrade Park Budget, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Denny Regrade Park - Construction Meetings Reports, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Denny Regrade Park: Project Files, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Denny Regrade Park Project File Jan. - March, 1978 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Denny Regrade Park Project File April - Dec, 1978 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Denny Regrade Park Project File, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Denny Regrade Park Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historical Information, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contracts Agreements, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contract - Architect, 1973 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Design Services Contract, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Design Services Contract, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contract - Project Management, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contract - Construction, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Security Reports, 1972 (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Progress Reports Project Administrator, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Construction Progress Reports, 1973 (Box-folder 13/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Construction Progress Reports, 1974 (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Master Plan, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 13/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Bureau of Outdoor Recreation Application, 1971 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: US Bureau of Outdoor Education, 1973 (Box-folder 13/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Bureau of Outdoor Recreation Property Transfer, 1979 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Application for Surplus Federal Property (Uplands), 1974 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Property Transfer - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Property Transfer Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Uplands), 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Property Rights Acquisition, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: U.S. Govt. / Surplus Property, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Capehart Housing, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access Road Alternatives A Planning Engineering Study, 1973 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Access Maps, 1972 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access U.S. Army Jan - May, 1973 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access U.S. Army June, 1973 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access U.S. Army July - Oct., 1973 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: U.S. Army, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: U.S. Army / Military Museum, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: U.S. Dept. of the Army Access, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: U.S. Dept. of the Army Licenses for use of Carolina St. or Texas Way, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access Road, 1975 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access Road Construction, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Access Road Construction Jan - July, 1981 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Entrance Road Construction July - Dec., 1981 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: METRO - West Point Joint Use, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: METRO, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: METRO Bus Service, 1975 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG - Antenna Site, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Antenna Site Improvements USCG, 1979 (Box-folder 14/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site - Surplus Land Application, 1980 (Box-folder 14/25)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site Improvements, 1980 (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site Improvements, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/27)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site Improvements, 1983 (Box-folder 14/28)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site Improvements, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: USCG Antenna Site Contracts Agreements, 1984 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1977 (Box-folder 14/31)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: City Light Property Rights, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14/32)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Utilities, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Utility Systems (includes map), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Utilities, 1974 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Neighborhood Playground, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Maintenance, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Parking - South Gate, 1973 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Parking Study, 1976 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Fish Habitat Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Environmental Impact Statement, 1972 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Environmental Impact Statement, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Environmental Impact Statement, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Environmental Impact Statement - Ad Hoc Committee, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel in the Pines, 1973 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel in the Pines, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel in the Pines Deeds Programs of Utilization, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel on the Hill, 1978 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel on the Hill, 1979 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chapel on the Hill, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Building Demolition Jan. - May, 1980 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Building Demolition July - Dec, 1980 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Building Demolition, 1981 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Discovery Park Sludge Lagoon, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: North South Beach Trail - Contracts, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: North Beach Trail, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: North Beach Trail, 1982 (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Discovery Park: North Beach Trail, 1983 (Box-folder 15/26)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: North Beach Trail - Draft supplemental impact statement preliminary schematic plan, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 15/27)
  - Discovery Park - South Beach Trail, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes Lease Agreement, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center dedication Site agreement - Photographs, 1971 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center Outdoor Component, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center Outdoor Component State of Washington Interagency Committee for Outdoor Recreation, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center - Land Use Access, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center - Economic Feasibility Studies, 1973 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center - Master Plan, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center Construction, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Daybreak Star Indian Cultural Center - Cree Construction Claim, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes, 1975 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes Jan. - August, 1976 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes Sept. - Dec., 1976 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: United Indians of All Tribes, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Indian Cultural Center - Parking, 1986 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District, 1978 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District, 1979 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District Adaptive Reuse Study Contract, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District, 1980 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District Jan - April, 1981 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District May - December, 1981 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District, 1982 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Historic District, 1983 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Archeological Study (includes contract), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Comfort Stations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Horse Patrol, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Citizens Advisory Committee, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Advisory Council, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Community Relations - Lawton Wood / Bay Terrace Access, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Lawton Park Neighborhood Lawton Wood, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Park Fact Finders, 1973 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Friends of Discovery Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Community Relations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Golf Courses, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Golf Course, 1975 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Nature Program, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Coughlin et al, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: M. Coughlin et al, 1979 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: M. Coughlin et al - Order, Hearing, Findings, and Decision Appeal, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Coughlin et al Witness Exhibits, 1983 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Coughlin et al Environmental Documents, 1983 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: M. Coughlin et al, Motions Notices, 1983 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: M. Coughlin et al, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Junior League, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Dahlias, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Rhododendron Forest, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 17/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Rhododendron Forest, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 17/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Park Opening, 1973 (Box-folder 17/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Briefing Information, 1973 (Box-folder 17/25)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Requests for Park Use, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 17/26)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Capital Development, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/27)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Interpretive Material, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/28)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Reports Studies, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 17/29)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Jan. - April, 1964 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File May - December, 1964 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Jan - Sept., 1969 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Oct. - Dec., 1969 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File, 1970 (Box-folder 18/8)